http://www.cna.com/web/guest/cna/cnadisclaimer?sub=privacypolicy

Industries
We provide deep expertise, attentive service and tailored business insurance solutions to help manage exposures and minimize loss across a wide array of industries.
Read More >
Construction
Financial Institutions
Healthcare
Law Firms
Life Sciences
Manufacturing
Professional Services
Real Estate
Technology
Products
& SolutionsOur wide range of business insurance products and solutions are specialized to meet the insurance and risk management needs of any business around the world.Read More >
Products
Products
Casualty
CNA Connect (Businessowners Policy)
CNA Paramount (Commercial Package)
CNA Surety
Commercial Auto
Cyber
Equipment Breakdown
General Liability
Management & Professional Liability
Marine
Property
Risk Control
With an average of more than 20 years of experience, CNA Risk Control professionals drive a program of systematic, sustainable risk control solutions designed to increase productivity and help protect your bottom line.
Read More >
Access Download Libraries for:
Risk Related to People
Risk Related to Property, Assets & Products
Risk Related to Professional & Management Liability
Additional Tools & Information:
PrepWise
School of Risk Control Excellence (SORCE)
Allied Vendors
CNA Blog - From the Experts
eSight
Agent LoginSecure logins, public resources - everything you need to quickly get to the information you need.
CNA Central
Agent Center
Lawyersinsurance.com
CNASurety.com
eSight
Home
PAY MY BILL
CLAIM CENTER
Industries
We provide deep expertise, attentive service and tailored business insurance solutions to help manage exposures and minimize loss across a wide array of industries.
Read More >
Construction
Financial Institutions
Healthcare
Law Firms
Life Sciences
Manufacturing
Professional Services
Real Estate
Technology
Products
& SolutionsOur wide range of business insurance products and solutions are specialized to meet the insurance and risk management needs of any business around the world.Read More >
Products
Products
Casualty
CNA Connect (Businessowners Policy)
CNA Paramount (Commercial Package)
CNA Surety
Commercial Auto
Cyber
Equipment Breakdown
General Liability
Management & Professional Liability
Marine
Property
Risk Control
With an average of more than 20 years of experience, CNA Risk Control professionals drive a program of systematic, sustainable risk control solutions designed to increase productivity and help protect your bottom line.
Read More >
Access Download Libraries for:
Risk Related to People
Risk Related to Property, Assets & Products
Risk Related to Professional & Management Liability
Additional Tools & Information:
PrepWise
School of Risk Control Excellence (SORCE)
Allied Vendors
CNA Blog - From the Experts
eSight
Agent LoginSecure logins, public resources - everything you need to quickly get to the information you need.
CNA Central
Agent Center
Lawyersinsurance.com
CNASurety.com
eSight
{}
hiddenheader
Web Content Viewer (JSR 286)
CNA Disclaimer
Privacy Policy
Last revised on: August 12, 2015
CNA and its affiliates (collectively, "CNA") value your privacy. It is important for you to understand how CNA collects, uses, discloses, and safeguards the information you may provide when you visit www.cna.com ("the CNA Website") and the services offered thereon, including but not limited to, CNA's social media platforms (collectively, the "CNA Services"). The CNA Online Privacy Policy (the "Privacy Policy") only applies to information collected through the CNA Services. For example, the Privacy Policy does not cover information you may provide to an independent CNA insurance broker outside of your use of the CNA Services. Other privacy policies, contractual provisions, or agreements you have entered into, including those with an independent CNA insurance broker, may apply depending on your relationship with CNA, your relationship with an independent CNA broker, your correspondence with other websites you visit, and your jurisdiction.
Personal Information
How CNA May Use Personal Information
How CNA May Disclose Personal Information
How CNA May Collect Other Information
How CNA May Use and Disclose Other Information
Third Party Services and Websites
Children's Privacy
Sweepstakes, Contests, and Other Promotions
Jurisdiction
Safeguarding Personal Information
Social Security Protection Privacy Statement
Updates to this Online Privacy Policy
Access and Correction of Personal Information
Personal Information
"Personal Information" is information that identifies you as an individual. Personal Information may include, depending on the circumstances, your name, postal address, phone number, email address, employment information, educational history, credit history, social security number, driver's license number, credit or debit card number, policy or claim information (including medical or health information you may provide), and criminal history information.
If you submit any Personal Information relating to other people to CNA or to CNA's service providers, you represent and warrant that you have the authority to do so and to permit CNA to use the information you provide.
How CNA May Use Personal Information
CNA may use Personal Information:
To contact or send you information you have opted to receive about CNA products and services.
To contact you at a telephone number, mobile number, postal address, or email address you provide to CNA. CNA may contact you in person, by recorded message, email, or by any other means of communication you agree to receive, as allowed by law and for reasonable business purposes.
To process claims you have submitted using the CNA Services.
To service your insurance needs.
To process employment applications you submit using the CNA Services.
To confirm or correct information you have submitted.
To help CNA prevent fraud and other crimes.
To comply with applicable laws and legal process, including responding to court, regulatory or governmental requests.
To personalize your experience while using the CNA Services.
To inform you of CNA job opportunities and to evaluate your suitability for a job.
To facilitate the social sharing functionality on CNA's social media platforms.
To enable you to participate in sweepstakes, contests and other promotions (see "Promotions, Sweepstakes, and Other Promotions" below).
To protect CNA's privacy, property, and that of you or others.
As otherwise allowed or required by law.
How CNA May Disclose Personal Information
CNA may disclose your Personal Information:
Within the CNA family of companies.
To third parties to assist with the management and service of CNA's business and the provision of CNA Services. The third parties may include, but are not limited to, agents or brokers, claims management service providers, employment application service providers, other insurance companies, regulators, administrators, and service providers that provide services, such as website hosting, data analysis, payment processing, information technology and the provision of related infrastructure, and email delivery.
To insurance support organizations and consumer reporting agencies. Information CNA shares with such organizations, such as claim history, may be retained by those organizations and disclosed to others as needed to provide CNA Services.
To third parties to market their products and services to you, only if you have given CNA permission to do so.
By you, on message boards, chat, profile pages, blogs, and other services to which you are able to post information (including, without limitation, on CNA's social media platforms). Please note that any information you post or disclose through CNA's social media platforms or elsewhere may become public information and may be available to the general public. CNA urges you to be careful when deciding to disclose your Personal Information or any other information on the CNA Services or elsewhere.
To a third party in the event of any reorganization, merger, sale, joint venture, assignment, transfer or other disposition of all or any portion of CNA's business, assets or stock (including in connection with any bankruptcy or similar proceedings).
As CNA determines necessary or appropriate: (a) under applicable law, including laws outside your country or territory of residence; (b) to comply with legal process; (c) to respond to requests from public, governmental, and regulatory authorities, including such requests initiated outside of your country or territory of residence; (d) to enforce CNA's Terms and Use; (e) to protect CNA's operations; (f) to protect CNA's rights, privacy, safety or property, and/or that of you or others; (g) to detect and prevent fraud; and (h) to allow CNA to pursue available remedies or limit damages CNA may sustain.
As otherwise allowed by law.
How CNA May Collect Other Information
CNA and its third party service providers may collect Other Information, including, but not limited to:
Through your browser, computer, or other device: Certain information is collected by most browsers or automatically through your computer or device, such as your Internet protocol (IP) addresses and Internet browser type and version.
From Cookies:  A cookie is a piece of information that is stored directly on the device you are using to access the CNA Services. Cookies allow for the collection of information, including browser type, time spent using the CNA Services, pages visited, date/time stamp, clickstream data, and other anonymous traffic data. Such information is used for security purposes, to facilitate navigation, to improve the design and functionality of the CNA Services, to provide information more effectively, and to personalize your experience while using the CNA Services. Cookies also enable CNA to select which of CNA's advertisements or offers are most likely to appeal to you and display them while you are using the CNA Services. If you do not want information collected through the use of cookies, you may decline cookies or decline the transfer to your computer of cookies from a particular site. Please refer to http://www.allaboutcookies.org/manage-cookies/index.html for more information. If you set your browser to reject cookies, you may then be required to re-enter certain information each time you visit the CNA Services.
How to Refuse the Use of Cookies
You may refuse the use of cookies by selecting the appropriate settings in your browser. However, if you do this you may lose some useful functionality such as personalization and "keep me signed in" and "remember me" features.
From you: Information you may provide, such as your preferred means of communication, which may be collected when you voluntarily provide that information. Unless combined with Personal Information, this information does not personally identify you or other users of the CNA Services.
How CNA May Use and Disclose Other Information
CNA may disclose Other Information when legally required to do so. If CNA is legally required to treat Other Information as Personal Information, then CNA may use that information as described in the "How CNA May Collect Other Information" section above, as well as for the purposes disclosed in this Online Privacy Policy with respect to Personal Information.
Third Party Services and Websites
From time to time, the CNA Services may include links to third party websites. This Online Privacy Policy does not apply to Other Information or Personal Information you provide to third party websites. CNA is not responsible for the privacy or other practices of any third party website. The inclusion of a link on the CNA Services to a third party website does not constitute CNA's endorsement of any linked third party website or services offered thereon. Specifically, CNA is not responsible for the collection, usage, or disclosure policies and practices (including the data security practices) of any third party website, including, but not limited to, Facebook, Linked, Twitter, or any other social media platform provider or operating system provider relating to Personal Information you may disclose through or in connection with any such third party website, including CNA's social media platforms.
Children's Privacy
The CNA Website and the CNA Services are not intended for use by minors, including children under the age of thirteen, and CNA does not knowingly collect Personal Information from such individuals.
Sweepstakes, Contests, and Other Promotions
CNA may sponsor or facilitate contests, sweepstakes or other promotions (any, a "Promotion," and collectively, "Promotions") on or through the CNA Services, CNA's social media platforms, or otherwise. Participation in such Promotions is purely voluntary. In order to participate in a Promotion, you may be asked to provide certain Other Information or Personal Information. By participating in a Promotion, you agree to the Promotion's terms and conditions or official rules, including those that pertain to the collection and/or use of Other Information and Personal Information. Also, by participating in a Promotion, you acknowledge that CNA is not responsible for actions or policies of third party sponsors or prize providers relating to the use of your Other Information or Personal Information in connection with the Promotion.
Jurisdiction
CNA is a worldwide company that conducts business in many different countries. It is CNA's policy to comply with the privacy laws and regulations of every jurisdiction in which CNA conducts business. This Online Privacy Policy only applies to CNA Services offered by CNA in the United States, and is not intended to subject CNA to the laws or jurisdiction of any state, territory, or country other than that of the United States. If you are viewing the CNA Services from outside the United States, this Online Privacy Policy may not apply. If you are accessing CNA's website in Canada, the following privacy policy may apply: www.cnacanada.ca/web/guest/canada/home/privacy.
Safeguarding Personal Information
CNA uses reasonable technical and administrative measures to protect Personal Information. No data transmission or storage system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have reason to believe that Personal Information you provided to CNA is no longer secure, please immediately notify CNA by contacting CNA's Security Control and Communication Center at 866-262-6244.
Social Security Protection Policy Statement
CNA seeks to protect the confidentiality of social security numbers ("SSN's") by maintaining physical, electronic, and procedural safeguards, and limits access to SSN's to help protect against their loss, misuse or unlawful disclosure.
Updates to this Online Privacy Policy
CNA reserves the right to change this Online Privacy Policy at any time in its sole discretion. The "revised" legend at the top of this web page indicates when the last revision was made. Any changes become effective upon notice thereof, which may be given by any reasonable means, including by posting a notice on the CNA Website. Your use of the CNA Services followi ng changes to this Online Privacy Policy means that you accept the terms of the revised Online Privacy Policy.
Access and Correction of Personal Information
If you want to access or correct the Personal Information that CNA has collected about you in connection with your use of the CNA Website or CNA Services, or if you have questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact CNA directly via email at compliance@cna.com.
© 2015 CNA. All rights reserved.
cnacontent/SA-CNAcom/SA-FatFooter/SA-TermsOfUse/CT-TermsOfUse
Terms of Use
IMPORTANT NOTICE: CNA would like to place cookies on your computer to improve your use of this website. To learn more, see our Privacy Statement. By continuing to use this website you shall be deemed to have consented to our use of cookies and to have accepted our website Privacy Policy.
Continue >>
/web/guest/cna/cnaform/!ut/p/b1/04_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJNDLy9Q3xMQo2M3Z3cDBwdHT2DAv1cDQ0sDPQLsh0VAfaYoTo!/?nID=Z6_40KKTL4U2B6D40Q1GIF71O2084&cID=Z6_40KKTL4U2B6D40Q1GIF71O2084&cnaSoloMode=true
/web/guest/cna/ClaimForms/!ut/p/b1/04_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJNDLy9Q3xMQo2CDLyNDBxdDbwD3ICku6epfkG2oyIA-fqI7Q!!/?nID=Z6_40KKTL4U2B6D40Q1GIF71O2084&cID=Z6_40KKTL4U2B6D40Q1GIF71O2084&cnaSoloMode=true
United States - English
LinkedInIcon
Twitter
By visiting our web site,you accept the terms and conditions as described in our Terms of Use.
Privacy
Statement | Conflict of Interest | Licensing
Disclosure | General Disclaimer | Privacy Policy | Sitemap | California Resident Privacy Policy
"CNA" is a service mark registered by CNA Financial Corporation with the United States Patent and Trademark Office. Certain CNA Financial Corporation subsidiaries use the "CNA" service mark in connection with insurance underwriting and claims activities. Copyright © Fri Dec 11 04:14:52 CST 2020 CNA. All rights reserved.
Please wait...
/web/guest/cna/findanagent/!ut/p/b1/04_Sj9CPykssy0xPLMnMz0vMAfGjzOJNDLy9Q3xMQo2c_DwNDRz9_YGEn6mBr5mhvp9-QbajIgAyUYsY/?nID=Z6_40KKTL4U2B6D40Q1GIF71O2084&cID=Z6_40KKTL4U2B6D40Q1GIF71O2084&cnaSoloMode=true
/web/wcm/connect/f9cb0d27-635b-44bd-84ff-39a2438fba6d/FAAgent_overlay_prod.png?MOD=AJPERES
/web/wcm/connect/85785d5f-e0ec-4f69-9314-05de5913a751/Find-an-agent-large+1024+X+175.jpg?MOD=AJPERES
